Nobody tells you this when you first start dirt biking.
The hard part is not about learning how to ride,
it's actually finding somebody who gets it.
My first real ride was brutal, it was 100 degrees outside, I was sweating through everything, my legs were shaking, my hands were tired, and honestly I could barely stay on the bike.
But you know what the crazy thing is, I couldn't stop thinking about it.
That's when I realized dirt biking is addictive.
And it gets even better when you have somebody to share it to.
However, most of what I found online felt scattered, outdated, or just not the way I wanted to be built.
So as a software engineer, I set out to do the one thing I know how. To build DirtBikeX
myself. The kind of place I wish existed. It's got no bloat. You don't have to post
the same thing twice. 21 languages. All the good stuff.
Most importantly, a real chance for us to be seen by fellow riders, so if you've been looking
for dirt bike people like me, go and check out the invite code in the description. My name is Rubio
and I'll be waiting for you there!