You can't show up to a dirt bike event you never discover, and honestly, that's what I felt as a new rider.
If you don't already know the track name, follow the right Instagram page, or know somebody who's plugged in,
you might just never find out there's a ride day happening right next to you.
And that's one of the reasons why I'm building DirtBikeX.
I want tracks to be easier to find, and exactly where riders are looking.
Here, if you run a dirt bike track, you can get verified as a track owner so riders know your updates are real.
You can create ride days, races, open practices, and even reoccurring events.
Then, fellow riders can find them in the Events tab, filter what's nearby, RSVP, and get reminded before it starts.
The idea is simple, help riders find places to ride, and help tracks to get more people to show up.
My name is Rubio, and if you're a track owner, comment "OWNER" and I'll send you the link!