Riders, you know what time it is when the bike starts screaming.
Yep, you don't stay in the same gear, you kick it up a notch.
And that's exactly the idea behind Verified Boost Rider.
And yes, DirtBikeX is always the real home to free riders, and the verified boost rider is for the people who want the next layer, the flair, the stats, the custom invites, and the insider hacks.
Once you get the membership, you can go ahead and go to Profile Edit and set up your custom flair so others know you're verified
You can bring fellow riders in with stronger invite tools, your custom invite code, and you get to see who actually accepted.
And if you hold a sponsorship pass, you get deeper stats.
Previous months, faster updates, and more insight into who actually engaged with your spot.
Boost Rider also get a special group chat, early updates, and features I'm testing with the community first.
So no, you don't need this to enjoy the community, but if you want to be part of what I'm building,
I can guarantee you this will help shape it.
My name is Rubio, and if you want to become one, follow and go check out my link in
the bio.