I build ad slots in my app because I hate ads.
Yup, I know how that sounds, so let me explain.
I could've made DirtBikeX full of flyers and banners, and honestly, that'd be the easy way out.
But I hate ads so much that I literally look away or close my eyes so that they don't get into my head
And I definitely want no riders opening my app and feel like they walked into a damn billboard.
So these slots work differently. There are limited passes for real riders who actually belong in the sport.
Here, you can go to the Sponsorship page and pick your spots.
Choose when it starts, choose how long it runs, and DirtBikeX got you covered.
Then, your profile will show up in multiple places across the app where people are actively looking
And the biggest one is the splash screen, where users can pause it, tap your face, and go straight into your profile.
And don't worry, to keep it fair, passes are capped and rotated, so nobody gets to flood the scene.
And you even get to check your sponsorship stats too.
Regional exposure, daily trends, you name it.
So essentially, it's a fair way to get seen by the right people.
My name is Rubio, and I'm giving out day passes for free.
Comment "PASS", and I'll see you in the app.